[Music]
[âm nhạc]
Hello, hello Dad, the Lunar New Year is almost here,
Alo Alo ba ơi ba Tết cũng sắp đến rồi cả
our whole family is bustling with excitement. As for Grandma and Grandpa, we're
nhà ta xôn xao rộn ràng Còn với ông bà
going to buy new clothes, and I'm ready to clean the
đi mua áo mới mê cung gì cô sẵn sàng dọn
house. There are firecrackers, peach blossoms, oranges,
nhà nào là pháo cánh đào nào là quả cam
pomelos, kumquats, and balloons. Hello, hello Dad, are you
quả bưởi cây quất và bóng bay Alo Alo ba
coming home soon? Our whole family is waiting for you. The Lunar New Year is here,
ơi ba ba sắp về chưa cả nhà ta chờ mong
making everyone in the neighborhood happy. We're
ba về tết đến rồi làm trên xóm dưới vui
taking off our pants, and we're still waiting. Hello, hello, there are
cởi quần bên này mãi chưa alo alo có
lots of gifts! Here are the New Year's gifts, this one is for
nhiều quà 3 đây là quà tết quà này cho
Grandma and Grandpa, and this one is for Mom and me.
ông bà và phần này là của mẹ với con Cả
Our whole family is in your heart, Dad.
Nhà mình ở trong tim ba
I'm waiting for you to come home.
ơi con đợi ba về
Dad, I'm waiting for you.
Ba ơi con đợi ba
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
Wishing Grandma and Grandpa long and healthy lives.
cầu chúc cho ông bà sống lâu sống khỏe
Wishing the children to study hard
nhá cầu chúc cho con trẻ chăm học chăm
and be well-behaved.
ngoan và cầu Bách gia thịnh vượng vạn sự
Wishing the whole family prosperity and everything goes as planned. Wishing a peaceful and loving home.
luôn Như Ý cầu chúc cho một nhà bình an
Hello, hello Dad, the Lunar New Year is almost here,
Alo Alo ba ơi ba Tết cũng sắp đến rồi cả
our whole family is bustling with excitement. As for Grandma and Grandpa, we're
nhà ta xôn xao rộn ràng Còn với ông bà
going to buy new clothes, and I'm ready to clean the
đi mua áo mới mê cung gì cô sớm sang dọn
house. There are firecrackers, peach blossoms, oranges, pomelos,
nhà nào là pháo cánh đào nào đó qua cam
pants, and balloons. Hello, hello Dad, are you
qua bưởi tới quần và bóng bay Alo Alo ba
coming home soon?
ơi ba ba sắp về chưa
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
Our whole family is in  My dear
cả nhà mình ở trong tim anh
Dad, I'm waiting for you to come home. Dad, I'm
Ba ơi con đợi ba về
waiting for you to come home. I love you, I love you. When you come home, you
Ba ơi con đợi ba về con yêu con yêu khi
'll take Grandma and Grandpa and the whole family
bao về mà sẽ đưa ông bà cùng cả nhà ta
to the temple to pray for blessings, wishing Grandma and Grandpa
lên chùa cầu phúc cầu chúc cho ông bà
long and healthy lives, wishing the
sống lâu sống khỏe nhá cầu chúc cho con
children to study hard and be well-behaved, and wishing the whole family prosperity and everything to go as planned.
trẻ chăm học chăm ngoan và cầu Bách gia
Wishing
thịnh vượng vạn sự luôn Như Ý cầu chúc
a peaceful and loving home.
cho một nhà bình an yêu thương ngập tràn
Wherever Grandma is, our family will always be like our name, "Reunion." The
Dù bà ở đâu thì nhà mình vẫn như tên
whole family will go to the temple to pray for blessings,
Đoàn viên cả nhà ta đến chùa cầu phúc
wishing Grandma and Grandpa long and healthy lives, wishing
cầu chúc cho ông bà sống lâu sống khỏe
the children to study hard and be well-behaved,
nhá cầu chúc cho con trẻ chăm học chăm
and wishing the whole family prosperity and everything to go
ngoan và cầu Bách gia thịnh vượng vạn sự
as planned. Wishing a peaceful home.
luôn Như Ý cầu chúc cho một nhà bình an
[Music]
[âm nhạc]